<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AIESEC</string>
    <string name="fragment1text">Hello, this is AISEC VIt chapter. We do a lot of work related to a lot of people and we go to places and hangout all over the world</string>
    <string name="about_aiesec_content">AIESEC is the world’s largest youth run organization which has been activating potential for 69 years  and has approximately 70,000 members in 126 countries and territories and has delivered over  480,000 experiences to date. \n\n We are a non-governmental not-for- profit organization that has been endorsed by the United  Nations, multiple presidents world-wide, CEOs of multinational corporations and recognised by  UNESCO.</string>
    <string name="about_aiesec">About AIESEC</string>
    <string name="about_vision">OUR VISION</string>
    <string name="aiesec_vision_content">Our vision and motto is “We strive to achieve peace and fulfilment of humankind’s potential.” by  providing the youth a platform to develop their leadership skills and promoting cross-cultural global  exchanges with a focus of creating a positive impact on society. \n\n We believe that it is every young person’s responsibility to take a positive role shaping the future of  our planet and everyone deserves the chance, and tools, to fulfil their potential. We provide young  people with self-driven, practical, global experiences. We empower them to see the world, have a  genuine effect and find what really matters to them.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ogetText"><![CDATA[Outgoing Global Entrepreneur provides a platform for enabling transformation  through an entrepreneurial experience in start up environments abroad. The  duration of the experience ranges from 6 weeks until 12 weeks. Depending on  the project accepted for, a stipend may or may not be provided. Are you ready  to venture into the world full of opportunities unexplored ?  In the race to be better than the best, we need to do things even best can&#39;t  imagine. Taking the road less travelled is not just a myth anymore. Technical  internships abroad is the way forward to stand out.  Outgoing Global Talent allows you to work for 3 to 18 months in a corporate  environment with regards to various fields of interests with a regulated stipend  depending on the project accepted for.  With flexible timelines and a world full of possibilities what are you waiting for?]]></string>
</resources>
